Aloha so here's our completed stepper circuit you'll see we've made some changes some of the
changes we made we have an input called reset okay and the reset goes into this or we have a clock
and what we're doing with the clock we're taking into an or so we have two ores for input we're
going to take clock and put it into an or and then negate it and put it into another or I'm
going to tie those ores to the odds and the evens or the first ones of every pair and the second
ones of every pair so every time we do clock we're going to cycle through our clock so let me do this
simulate reset it
so every time we're just going to cycle through this so every time I do clock it's going to switch
between one and then when I go to zero it'll do the second one one zero one zero one zero one zero
and it just keeps walking down okay so let me reset and explain how this works okay so I have
this reset all right and it comes in and it is also into the or for set one set two and it's negated
into CPU one okay so when I click reset goes high notice that one is on okay if I go low so I reset
it one is still on because the output from the first pair is zero and I negate it and it goes
into the or now if I go high on one it's going to pass that one to the second one high on the output
it'll make step two and then because this is negated so this is a plus one this becomes zero
again high pass it down one low on clock
passes it out the second part and that goes into step three now we're taking this as an and now
it was an or again this would always be one because this is going to stay one
so we're making an and and so this one becomes zero and this becomes zero
so then we can just go clock clock step four clock clock step five
clock clock
Step six, clock, clock, step seven, all right?
And so we've cycled through all seven.
Then what we're gonna wanna do
and is we're gonna wanna look at our circuit appearance,
which I'll show you a diagram
and maybe it'll look something like this.
Okay, I have a clock on the left, reset on the right
and then I have my seven outputs, all right?
And now what I'm gonna do is probably at some point,
I'll not change the appearance,
but what I'll do is I'll take the output from seven
and put it into reset.
And that way when seven goes high, reset goes high
and it resets the whole thing and we start over, all right?
So that's pretty much how the stepper works
and drawing it up.
Hopefully you walk through it
and it makes sense to you on how the stepper works
because this is how we're gonna choose what we're doing.