Aloha.
So what I want to do is show a little bit about how
this stepper is going to work and discuss a little bit.
So I have my little unit I have with
the two memory bits tied together,
and what I'm going to show you is how this chain works.
So right now the input to the first one is zero.
So let me change the input to one and I hit set one.
Now, every other memory item is connected to set one.
So the first one of every pair is connected to set one.
So I'm going to set that so that the output is one,
turn my input off, and then I'm going to set two.
What set two is going to do is it's tied to
the memory bit of every even one,
so two, four, six, eight,
or the second one of every pair.
So what that will do, we'll pass that input one
that's stored in the first one,
it'll pass it to the output,
which will be the first item,
and pass it as the input to the next one.
So then we'll turn set two off and then just go set one again,
which will pass it to the second part,
and pass the zero into the second one.
So that's set one of the first one,
and then I'll hit set two again,
and it'll turn off the first item and turn on the second item.
I'll turn that off, I'll go set one to pass it down one,
set two to turn off the second one and go to the third one.
And so I just keep cycling, set one on off,
set two on off, move to the next one, set one on off,
set two on off, move to the next one, move to the next one, move to the next one.
Set one on off, move to the next one, move to the next one, move to the next one.
Set one on off, set two on off, move to the last one,
and then set one on off, set two on off,
sends the zero, so they're all back to zero.
Okay, so that's how the stepper works.
It's gonna just step through,
and what we're gonna do is we're actually gonna tie
the output, this last one, back to the input
so that we actually just cycle through six.
So we're gonna add another one to the left foot.
Basically, this is how this works.
So that we are able to sequentially step through
different items, basically using the set one, set two,
set one, set two, set one, set two.
Okay, so that's how our stepper's gonna work.
And then I'll show you the finished circuit
and walk through how that works.
Thanks.